Let's show it to everyone.
みんなに見てもらおうね
I want you to see it.
見てほしいなぁ
I'm really mushy.
めっちゃムルムルしてる
I just called you when it was free,
さっきちょっと無料の時に電話やっただけで、
I've been there quite a few times.
結構一回いっちゃったから
The M word.
M字
M word?
M字?
Do you want me to?
してほしい?
So let's make a cuppa?
じゃあクパーしちゃう?
Enough?
もういい?
do.
して
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいんだけど
I'll make a cuppa, then.
クパーするよ、じゃあ
A little more under camera.
もうちょっとカメラ下で
appear?
見える?
Look?
見て?
appear?
見える?
So that you can see the hole.
穴るまで見えるように
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗でしょ?
Something like a face.
なんか顔
Is the camera a little lower?
カメラもうちょっと下?
It's difficult to see your face.
顔が映るのが難しいね
Pull it a little more.
もうちょっと引きで
Can you pull it out a little more?
もうちょっと引き?
Should I pull it?
私が引けばいいのか?
like this?
こう?
Something like this?
こういうこと?
I'm already getting all excited.
もうメラメラしちゃう
Kupa up.
クパーアップ
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Want to see it from your bag?
バッグからも見たい?
It's like this.
こんな感じ
There is also a door-up cuppa that fills the screen.
画面いっぱいのドアップクパーも
Door-up cuppa filling the screen.
画面いっぱいのドアップクパー
Like this?
こんな感じ?
It looks great.
めっちゃ見えるね
With two fingers.
2本指で
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's dangerous.
ヤバい
Hold my legs.
足抱えて
I like being tired like this.
こうやって疲れるの好き
When I was a normal person.
正常人の時
Do you understand?
分かる?
I'm glad you came.
来てよかった
thank you.
ありがとう
I think I'll try it with my fingers.
ちょっと指でしてみようかな
That's dangerous.
ヤバい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can you tell me what feels good?
どこが気持ちいいのか言えるかな?
The dog feels good.
ワンコ気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's dangerous.
ヤバい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
When I'm alone, I cut my middle teeth, both of them.
一人の時は、中歯くり、両方
Like a mouth.
口みたいな
No mouth.
口はダメ
Tell me what feels best.
一番気持ちいいとこ教えて
The most comfortable part is in the back.
一番気持ちいいのは奥
I like the back.
奥が好き
Wish for Kupa at the front.
正面でクパーを願う
In front.
正面で
The mouth hole is also clean.
口の穴もきれい
mouth hole.
口の穴
I'll make this a side dish for Minami's dog.
みなみのワンコおかずにするよ
Please have it as a side dish.
おかずにしてください
I want to put my cock in Minami's dog.
みなみちゃんのワンコにチンポ入れたいよ
I want you to include it.
入れて欲しい
Look, I want a dog now.
ほら、もうワンコ欲しくなったよ
I want a cock too.
私も欲しいチンポ
Dogs often say that they feel good.
ワンコ気持ちいいっていっぱい言うんだよ
good.
よかった
The dog feels good.
ワ ンコ気持ちいいよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I have your big one please?
おじさんの大きいのちょうだい?
Can I have your big one, please?
お じさんの大きいのちょうだい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
160 people are watching.
160人も見てるよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
copper?
どう?
Like this?
こんな感じ?
ah
ああ
It feels good.
気 持ちいいな
I'll do it because I want a rotor.
ローターしたくなっちゃったからするね
Isn't it the rotor?
ローターじゃないか
A phone?
電話か
Oh, it feels so good.
ああ、気持ちいい
Show me your dog hole.
ワンコの穴見せて
appear?
見える?
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Let's lower the camera.
カメラ下げよう
When you lower it, your face...
下げると顔が...
Should I go down?
私が下がればいいの?
This is it.
これって
difficult.
難しい
Oh, it feels so good.
ああ、気持ちいい
We've never been friends.
仲良ししたことない
I want you to include it.
入れて欲しいな
Perverts equal everyone.
変態イコールみんなに
He's a pervert.
変態だよ
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
The dog is going.
ワンコ行きます
I'm going.
行くんだよ
I want you to wake up.
体を起こして欲しいな
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh, it feels so good.
ああ、気持ちいい
We got along well.
仲良しした
Your waist will also grow.
腰も伸っちゃう
Chemp is hot.
チェンプは熱いんだ
I want to add Champ.
チェンプ入れたいな
From when you put the cushion on your back.
背中にクッション入れるときから
thank you.
ありがとう
Like this?
こんな感じ?
It's a color like this.
こんな感じの色ね
The dog is bright red.
ワンコ真っ赤だね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
While holding my legs.
足抱えながら
Like this?
こんな感じ?
I want you to lean against me.
腰を寄せて欲しいね
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Lower the back a little.
裏も少し下げて
This much?
このくらい?
Do you all want to play with dogs?
みんなワンコジュルジュルしたいの?
After sizzling.
ジュルジュルしてから
Does it hurt already?
もう痛いかな
big
大
There are big ones and small ones,
き いやつと小さいやつがあるんだけど、
Minamiha
み なみは
I like the bigger one, so I'll put in the bigger one.
大 きい方が好きなので、 大きい方を入れます
Try holding the build between your breasts.
ビルドをおっぱいで挟んでみてください
Like this?
こんな感じ?
I don't have breasts like that that can be pinched.
挟めるほうってそんなおっぱいないんだよね
amazing.
すごい
My breasts became slimy, too.
ぬるぬるになっちゃったよ、おっぱいも
Is everyone in a good mood?
みんな気上位がいいかな?
Well then, I'll put my best foot forward.
じゃあ気上位入れちゃうな
I might see this.
見るかも、これ
After getting excited, it's the M letter.
気上位してからM字ね
This is really tough.
これ めっちゃゴリゴリする
This is terrible.
これやばい
Not everyone likes it because it's so grindy.
すっごいゴリゴリするから、みんなもこれ好きじゃない
Let's use this one that's not too big.
こっちのあんまり大きくない方にしよう
I'm in, Paco.
入ったよ、パコ
This feels good.
気持ちいい、これ
I'm in, Paco.
入ったよ、パコ
appear?
見える?
If so, would I be able to play it?
あったら吹けるかな?
pa
パ
Is this possible?
ック でできました?
You can pack it.
パックできるよ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Okay.
よっしゃった
Really stick it out.
ほんと突き出して
It's really nice.
ほんとかいいな
It's like this.
こんな感じだよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Messed up around here.
めちゃくちゃ、この辺
Like squirting.
潮吹きみたいな
It's radio waves, so you can squirt at all.
電波だから潮吹けるよ、全然
Many points.
多 分
Thank you for the pack, I agree.
パ ックありがとう、お同意いたしまして
Beautiful pussy.
綺麗なマンコヤ
綺 麗 なマンコヤ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Spread it out until you have beer in it.
ビール入れておくまで広げて
Do you want to expand it?
広げるの?
like this?
こう?
Please let me support you.
支援させてください
Please wait a moment for some water.
ちょっと水のちょっと待っててください
I'm home.
ただいま
There were quite a few people who said that Dewdock was better.
なんかね、デュードックの方がいいって言ってくれた人が結構いた
However, it hurts when my nose comes out a little.
けど、 ちょっと鼻出るのちょっと痛い
I'm home.
ただいま
Show me your butt from behind, please.
バックでお尻見せて、お願い
Okay.
いいよ
Butt in the back.
バックでお尻
Good.
よいしょ
It's like this.
こんな感じ
I want Chikubizume to do a little more.
チクビズメのもうちょっとしてほしい
Do your best in a way that doesn't hurt.
痛くないやり方で頑張ってね
thank you.
ありがとう
Try spreading your anus.
アナル広げてみて
Okay.
いいよ
Let's spread it out as much as possible with the letter M.
M字でいっぱい広げよう
More up.
もっとアップ
That's crazy, look.
やばいね、見て
A mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃ
Look.
見て
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
Spread your legs out with both hands as if holding them.
足を抱えるように両手で広げて
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Just put your finger in it and spread it out from the inside.
少し指入れて中から広げるんだよ
yankeeswari.
ヤンキーズワリして
There have been people asking for Yankees Wari for a while now.
さっきからヤンキーズワリを求めてくる人がいるんだな
Yankees wari.
ヤンキーズワリ
Is this so?
こうですか?
Please lower the camera a little more and show me.
もう少しカメラ下げたらお見せてください
What are you going to do with this?
これで何するの?
Does it hurt?
むずくね?
I think it's going to go really well.
めっちゃ行くと思うんだけど
This is going really well.
これさ、めっちゃ行くよね
This feels good.
これ気持ちいい
I wonder if it's a little bit more.
もうちょっとしたかな
Will this blow a lot and then some more?
これがいっぱい吹いて、もっと吹いちゃう?
I'm sure it'll blow up a lot.
めっちゃ吹いちゃうよ、多分
Usually by shaking my hips.
大 抵腰振って
Like this?
こんな感じ?
This feels good.
気持ちいい、これ
That's why the build is good.
それでビルドがいい
Sorry that the build is a little rough.
ビルドちょっと痛くてごめんね
Everyone is looking forward to Minami's perversion.
みなみの変態みんな期待してるからね
It's frustrating that people have high expectations for me.
期待してくれてるのもどっかしい
Please give me permission to take a photo.
写真許可をください
You can't go yet.
まだまだ行っちゃダメだよ
Minami hasn't gone yet either.
みなみもまだ行ってないよ
I want to go with you.
一緒に行きたいな
He's a pervert, he's a pervert.
変態だね、変態です
Just do it once and go.
一回そのままくりで行ってね
Okay.
いいよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
If it's a small one, this will fit just fine.
小さいやつなら、これならギリギリ入るけど
This jaggedness is a bit painful.
ちょっとこのギザギザが痛い
I like the real thing.
本物がいいんだね
After all, the real thing is better.
本物がいいやっぱり
Very honest.
めっちゃ正直
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I wish it had rubber.
ゴムあればいいんだけどね
I did it manually.
手動かしながらやって
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Put your hands behind your head.
手を頭の後ろで組んで
How many people complained about Minami?
みなみの文句何人出たの?
full.
いっぱい
Slowly and tightly.
ゆっくりぎゅっとして
If you want me to include your live performance that much, I'll include it.
ライブそんなに入れて欲しいんだったら入れてあげるよ
It hurts just a little bit.
痛いからちょっとだけね
I don't really like this.
あんまり好きじゃないし、これ
I really like the real thing.
やっぱ本物がいい
I like the real thing.
本物がいいよ
I'll be very honest though.
めっちゃ正直に言っちゃうけど
Good.
よいしょ
A lot of lotion came out.
ちょっと ローションがいっぱい出てきた
Okay.
よ いしょ
I'll put it in, dick.
入れちゃうよ、ちんちん
Look.
ほら
Put it in slowly.
ゆっくり入れるんだよ
A slow seal.
ゆっくりのシール
Ah, I opened it.
あ、開けちゃった
Good.
よいしょ
a little bit.
ちょっと
Pull your finger lightly.
指軽く引っ張って
This really hurts.
やっぱこれ痛い
I guess I'll use my fingers.
指でしようかな
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
This is no good, it hurts.
これダメだ、痛い
It's a little painful and I can't do it.
ちょっと痛くて無理
Thank you, I'll call you.
ありがとう、電話にします
Waiting for the dildo to be shaken.
ディルド振られるの待ち
I like dildos, so we didn't get along well.
ディルド好きでなんか相性悪かった
Let's continue on the phone.
電話で連続行きしよう
Shall we go continuously?
連続行きしちゃおうか
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Normark loves phone calls.
ノーマークは電話大好きなの
It's terrible, really.
やばいよ、めっちゃ
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
Do one more thing.
もう1つして
nose?
鼻?
The chestnuts have gotten really big.
すごい栗が大きくなっちゃった
Oh, it's gone too far.
あー行き過ぎてやばい
Did everyone come out a lot?
みんないっぱい出た?
Put your hands behind your head and try to ignore it.
両手、頭の後ろに組んで無視してみて
Is it like this?
こういう感じ?
Mankoya certainly looks delicious.
確かにうまそうなマンコヤ
thank you.
ありがとう
Her boobs are also made of vinyl.
おっぱいもビニールだし
thank you.
ありがとう
I get a lot of compliments on my boobs.
おっぱいは結構褒められるんだよね
side.
脇
The side looks like this.
脇はこんな感じ
I want my hair to be a ponytail.
髪の毛ポニテにしてほしい
Okay, Ponytail.
いいよ、ポニテ
Good.
よいしょ
Okay.
よ いしょ
Po nite.
ポ ニテ
Minami is the strongest.
みなみ最強
thank you.
ありがとう
Ponytail.
ポニテ
It's amazing everyone compliments me.
すごいみんな褒めてくれるね
Please spread your pussy so I can see your anus.
アナル見えるようにおマンコ広げてください
I guess this is it.
こう かな
A little lower?
ちょっと下か
Okay.
よ い しょ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってな
Like this?
こんな感じ?
appear?
見える?
What does it mean to spread out in a triangle?
三角で広げるって何?
What is a triangle?
三角形って何?
Is it popular?
流行ってるの?
that.
それ
what?
何?
I don't know.
わかんない
Up to the anal limit.
アナル限界までアップして
To the anal limit.
アナル限界まで
Up to the anal limit.
アナル限界までアップして
appear?
見える?
That's terrible.
やばいね
good
よ い
Sho.
しょ
It would be dangerous if it were hexagonal.
六 角形してはやばいじゃん
I'm rolling this.
これ巻いてるよ
I went there a lot.
いっぱい行っちゃった
Are there any cute Japanese girls who are this naughty?
日本人可愛くてこんなエッチな子いるのかよ
Does it look like it's standing up?
立てに見えらす?
Something like this?
こういうこと?
It doesn't shake much though.
なんかあんま揺れないんだけど
Okay.
よ いしょ
I just want to see your mouth for a moment like this.
こんな一瞬だけを口見たいです
I'll definitely be able to read lips.
口はやっぱ読めよう
I just fell in love with it.
ちょっとただ惚れました
thank you.
ありがとう
A lot of sperm came out.
い っぱい精子出たぞ
Roll up to the limit.
巻き限界までアップ
I don't think I've ever met a girl this cute.
な かなかこんなに可愛い子は出会えないな
thank you.
ありがとう
mouth?
口?
I want to see your mouth that much.
そんなに口見たいな
Really cute ponytail.
本当にポニット可愛い
thank you.
ありがとう
mouth?
口?
Do you want to see it that much?
そんなに見たいの?
I can't show your mouth.
口は見せれないよ
Is it already over?
もう終わったんですか?
tears.
涙
I guess I can't go anymore.
もうね、いけないかな
It's like this.
こんな感じ
I don't show my skin.
肌は見せない
Then it's all there.
そうしたら全部じゃん
I went there a lot.
いっぱい行っちゃった
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
thank you.
ありがとう
Everyone said so many erotic things to me,
みんなにエロいことを言われすぎて、
I was really excited and went a lot.
すごい興奮していっぱい行っちゃいました
Finally, everyone.
最後、みんな
I think I'll make an M-shape.
M字しようかな
M-shaped in perspective.
M字してくパースで
Okay.
よ いしょ
Like this?
こんな感じ?
If you do this, everyone's wishes will come true.
これしたらみんなの願いを叶える
Want to see my butt too?
お尻も見たい?
Okay, ass.
いいよ、お尻
Butt.
お尻ね
They're separate.
別々なの
That's dangerous, right?
やばいでしょ?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I also want to do something naughty.
また、イッチなことしたいな
You have a beautiful pussy, so why not make it into a shaved pussy?
綺麗なマンコだからパイパンにしない?
I might not make it into a shaved pussy.
パイパンにはしないかも
I wonder if my shaved pussy will grow.
パイパンは育ちようかな
Do you like shaved pussy that much?
そんなにパイパン好き?
It was a very beautiful butt.
すごく綺麗なお尻でした
thank you.
ありがとう
I'll come back later.
また来ます
I'll definitely come.
絶対来る
thank you.
ありがとう
It was super good.
超よかった
thank you.
ありがとう
Please come again with your dick full.
また、おちんちんをパンパンにして来てね
Please provide more profile service.
もっと横顔サービスをお願い
Just a little.
ちょっとだけだよ
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Will it end?
終わるのか
It's over.
終わっちゃうよ
Did you finish the hour?
1時間終わりにしたの?
I wanted to see him standing.
立ち姿が見たかった
Standing.
立ち姿
My energy is really bothering me.
元気がすげえ邪魔だな
I'm sorry I just came.
今来たのに、ごめんね
Let's do it together again.
また一緒にやるのにしよう
I want the rest.
残り欲しい
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいあるね
It's a good top.
いいトップです
thank you.
ありがとう
Let's do lots of things that feel good.
気持ちいいこといっぱいしましょう
bye bye.
バイバイ
I'm so excited.
キ ュ ンです
bye bye.
バイバイ
see you.
またね
Okay.
いいよ
Come see my pussy again.
目の目のおまんこまた見に来てね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
see you.
またね
bye bye.
バイバイ
I don't know how to cut it.
切り方がわからなくなった
see you.
またね
bye bye.
バイバイ